本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Cinderella 猫 小犀
校对： cinderella   后期： 泡面小小
东区女巫前情提要...
Previously, on Witches of East End...
你的项链 变红了 这是你最后一条命了
Your necklace, it's red. This is your last life.
你也许应该走开了
You should probably move along now.
你不必这么做的 我可以自己照顾自己
You didn't have to do that. I can take care of myself.
你没什么可担心的
You have nothing to worry about.
我只是想确定我没有成为第三者
I just want to make sure I'm not getting in the middle of something.
只是一个吻而已
It was just a kiss,
我们绝对不会告诉任何人 因为这已经结束了
and we are never, ever going to tell anyone because it's over.
我在图书馆听到你的话了 我要一早去伦敦
I heard you at the library. I'm leaving early for London.
我不是你母亲 你认识我 我是雅典娜
I'm not your mother. You knew me as Athena.
- 我为什么会在这里? - 巨蛇座
- Why am I here? - Serpens clavem.
它是一条金色的蛇
It's a golden snake.
尾巴看起来像一把钥匙
The tail looks like a key.
我要你说服你姨妈把它交出来
I need you to convince your aunt to give it back.
只要你告诉我蛇钥匙在哪里 这一切就会结束
This will end if you tell me where the snake is.
它已经没了
It's gone.
她说一个是你的灵魂伴侣
She said one is your soul mate,
另一个 是你的冤家?
and the other, your destroyer?
意思是其中一个会把你杀死吗?
Does that mean one of them is gonna kill you?
这是个比喻 英格丽德 塔罗牌可是很狡猾的
It's a metaphor, Ingrid. Tarot cards are tricky that way.
你觉得基利安是你的冤家吗?
And you think Killian is the destroyer?
很明显啊 所有这些麻烦
Obviously. All this trouble
都始于我认识他的那晚
started the night I met him.
他就是我失去达什的原因 他当然是我的冤家
He's the reason I lost Dash. Damn right he's the destroyer.
...什么 两分钟 还...
...what, two minutes, and...
那 你打算怎么办?
So, what are you gonna do?
我能怎么办? 达什现在在伦敦
What can I do? Dash is in London.
他都不回我电话
He's not returning any of my calls.
他现在恨死我了... 是我活该
He hates me right now... And rightfully so.
- 请慢用 - 弗雷娅 我很抱歉
- Enjoy. - Freya, I'm so sorry.
没事 我不会让基利安毁了我的...
It's okay. I am not gonna let Killian destroy me...
我要把这些伤心都变成美好
I'm gonna trade all this heartbreak for good.
就像那对苦命夫妻一样 看
Like for that angry couple back there. Watch.
...一定有什么事...
...something that's been going on...
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
- 我们不要再这么做了 - 好
- Let's not do that again. - Okay.
你刚才做了什么?
What did you just do?
用点小心思 给他们一个"爱的突袭"
Gave 'em a "Rush of Love," with a twist.
天哪 你太棒了
Damn, you're good.
我的生活也许很混乱
My life may be in shambles,
不过至少我能让别人高兴起来
but at least I can make someone else happy.
花朵...
Flore...
凋零
Pulchre.
花朵..
Flore...
重生
Veneficus.
东区女巫 第一季第08集
- 温迪 - 嘿
- Wendy. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 怎么了?
- Hey. - What's up?
我要给你看一样东西
I need to show you something,
不过...
and, uh...
我希望你不要生我的气
I don't want you to get angry with me.
好吧 我为什么要生气呢?
Okay, why would I be angry?
入口钥匙?!
The portal key!?
究竟怎么回事! 你说过它已经被毁了的
What the hell! You said that was destroyed.
- 我说谎了 - 你说谎...?
- I lied. - You lied...?
就因为这把钥匙我被杀了!
I was killed over that key!
现在我只有最后一条命了
I'm on my last life now.
- 我很抱歉 - 你很抱歉!
- I am so sorry. - You're so sorry!
你向我保证不生气的
You promised me that you were not gonna get angry.
不 我没有
No, I didn't.
- 我听见你说了! - 不 我没说!
- I heard you! - No, I didn't!
你在干什么呢 乔安娜? 怎么回事?
What are you doing, Joanna? What happened?
为什么假冒者会以为是我偷了它?
And why did the shifter think that I stole it?
我不知道 不知道
I have no idea. I don't know.
- 乔... - 无疑阿奇博尔德想得到它
- Jo... - Archibald wanted it, for sure.
- 是吗? - 他甚至怀疑东西在我们这里
- Yeah? - And he even suspected that we had it,
不过他没想出它在什么地方
but he's never figured out where it was,
我已经把它藏了几百年了
and I've kept it hidden for centuries.
假冒者知道我们住在哪里 乔安娜
The shifter knows where we live, Joanna.
- 温迪 我搞砸了 - 对 你搞砸了
- Wendy, I messed up. - Yeah, you messed up.
我们密封了入口钥匙你却告诉我它已经被毁了
You told me that thing was destroyed after we sealed the portal.
我很相信你
I believed you.
我知道 我也说了...
I know. And like I said...
你说谎了
You lied.
你为什么要保留巨蛇座?
Why would you keep that snake?
它...
It's...
很诱惑很败坏又很讨厌
Seductive and corrupting and poisonous.
我们都知道它会对人们做出什么事
You and I both know what it does to people.
你为什么还一直保存着它?
Why would you keep it this whole time?
你以为你某天会用上它
You thought that you might use it again someday.
难以置信! 你还说我鲁莽呢
Unbelievable! And you call me the reckless one.
你知道我们再也回不去了 乔安娜
You know that we can never go back there, Joanna.
你为什么想回到过去呢?
Why would you want to?
现在我们的生活比以前好多了
Our lives so much better here.
我从没用过它 温迪 我也没打算用它
I've never used it, Wendy, I don't plan to use it,
不过我不会把它丢掉...
but I'm not getting rid of it...
这是我跟我们家族唯一的连结
It is my only connection with our home.
温迪...
Wendy...
我觉得这样很不好
I don't feel good about this.
- 嘿 抱歉我迟到了 - 嘿 没事 没事
- Hey. Sorry I'm late. - Hey. Oh, no problem, no problem.
发生什么事了? 弗雷娅的婚礼取消了吗?
So, what happened? Is Freya's wedding off?
也许 很可能
Maybe. Probably.
真希望我能帮上什么忙
Oh, I just wish there was something I could do to help.
好吧 要是能让你好受点的话
Well, if it makes you feel better,
有个人你还真能帮呢
there's someone else here that you can help.
他们想借书吗?
Do they want to check out a book?
貌似他想借的是你
Seems like he wants to check you out.
那是迈克
Oh, that's just Mike.
就是他在内战走廊救了你?
That's the guy that saved you in the Civil War aisle?
你没告诉我他有这么帅啊
You didn't tell me how cute he was.
- 你觉得帅吗? - 是啊
- You think so? - Yeah.
巴布 不 我... 我又不是在逛超市
Barb, no, I'm... I'm not in the market.
好吧 我不会说服你嫁给他
Oh, well, I'm not telling you to marry him.
我甚至不想让你跟他约会
I'm not even telling you to date him.
不过我希望你过去帮帮他
But I am telling you to go over there and help him.
嘿 迈克
Hey, Mike.
- 英格丽德 见到你很高兴 - 怎么了?
- Ingrid, I am so glad to see you. - What's going on?
我听说你很了解东区的历史
I hear you know a lot about the history of East End.
对 我研究过一些 你想知道什么?
I have studied some, yes. What do you want to know?
所有的一切
Everything.
我有一部历史虚构小说
My novel is historical fiction,
正进行到二十世纪之交
set here at the turn of the 20th century,
我很希望能借用一下专家的观点
and I could really use some insight from an expert.
我不确定能当专家 不过很乐意帮助你
Well, I'm not sure I'm an expert, but I would be happy to help.
太棒了
Great.
嘿
Hey.
达什的手没事吧?
How's Dash's hand?
我说你好
I said hello.
这里没有龙舌兰酒了 我想楼上会有
We're out of tequila. I think there's some more upstairs.
怎么 你就这样... 不跟我说话了吗?
So what, you're just... not gonna talk to me?
我说话了啊 我说这里没有龙舌兰酒了
I just did. I said we're out of tequila.
你怎么能生我的气呢?
How can you be mad at me?
这些又不是我的错 我又没告诉达什我们的事
None of this is my fault. I didn't tell Dash what happened.
你能诚实地看着我并且告诉我
Can you honestly look me in the eye
他发现之后你没觉得高兴吗?
and say you are not happy that he found out?
这就是你希望发生的事...
This is what you wanted to have happen...
不准...
Stop...
怪罪到我身上
Putting this on me.
听着 我做了所有你要求我做的事
Look, I've done everything you asked.
你想做朋友 我们做朋友了
You wanted to be friends, we're friends.
你让我向前看 我向前看了
You told me to move on, I moved on.
别搞得好像我毁了你的生活一样
Stop treating me like I screwed up your life.
就是这样! 你就是毁了我的生活!
You did! You destroyed it!
你以为我希望我哥哥恨我吗?
You think I want my brother to hate me?
你以为我希望你恨我吗?
You think I want you to hate me?
我不知道你想怎么样
I don't know what you want.
我想连你自己都不知道
I don't think you know what you want.
我觉得这一切对你来说都是个游戏
I think this whole thing is a game to you,
我再也不想参与了
and I am not doing it anymore.
嗨
Hi.
艾米...
Amy...
抱歉 我来看你工作原本是想给你个惊喜
Sorry, I thought I would surprise you at work.
好惊喜呢
Surprise.
也许我们不应该等到日落再把它埋了
Maybe we shouldn't wait until sundown to bury it.
也许我们本来就不应该埋它
Maybe we shouldn't bury it at all.
我觉得我们应该烧了它
I think we should just burn it.
要是我一个人处理掉这些你会觉得好受些吗?
Would you feel more comfortable if I took care of this without you?
不 如果它不存在我才会好受些
No, I'd feel more comfortable if it didn't exist.
你看见它是怎么对待我们父亲的
You saw what it did to our father.
它把他体内所有的东西都毁了
It killed everything good inside of him.
你不用盯着我看 我们不会销毁它的
We're not getting rid of it, so you can stop looking at me like that.
听着 乔安娜
Listen, Joanna,
我... 我理解你为什么保留着它
I... I understand why you kept it.
我真的理解
I do.
你以为要是你等得足够久 也许某一天
You thought if you waited long enough, that maybe someday
你就能利用它再见到弗雷德里克
you could use it so you could see Frederick again.
我不想谈弗雷德里克
I don't want to talk about Frederick.
你从来不想谈弗雷德里克
You never want to talk about him.
我知道你想他
I know that you miss him.
我不想谈论这些 我就不应该告诉你钥匙的事
I don't want to talk about it. I should never have told you about the key.
别管它了 我会处理好它的
So just leave it alone, and I'll take care of it.
温迪...
Wendy...
你干什么了?!
What did you do?!
它攻击我 快把它弄下来
It attacked me. Get it off right now.
- 哎呦! - 我在弄呢 我不想弄伤你
- Ow, ow, ow! - I'm trying. I don't want to hurt you.
到底怎么回事! 你看它的眼睛了吗?
What the hell happened! Did you look in its eyes?
你知道不该看它的眼睛的
You know you are not supposed to look in its eyes.
好了 我现在 实在是没心情听你说教
Okay, I am really, really not in the mood for one of your lectures right now.
解除巨蛇
Dimitte serpens.
这条蛇是纯粹邪恶的载体
This snake is a powerful vessel of pure evil.
我觉得我们需要一些更厉害的东西
I think we need something a little stronger
而不是即兴的拉丁咒语!
than off-the-cuff Latin commands!
我们试试讽刺吧 应该有帮助
Let's try sarcasm; that should help.
我去拿魔书
Let me get the Grimoire.
乔安娜
Joanna.
看啊
Look.
待着别动 我去把书拿来 我们会找到办法的
Stay right there. I'm getting the book. We'll figure this out.
快点
Hurry.
- 听着 基利安... - 天哪
- Look, Killian... - Oh, God.
"听着 基利安"后面从来没有好结果
No good conversation ever started with "Look, Killian..."
我喜欢你 真的 很喜欢
I really like you. I do. A lot.
我喜欢忧郁的男生 我对他们毫无抵抗力
I have a thing for lost souls. I'm... I'm a sucker for them.
但是我觉得我不是那个能找到你灵魂的人
But I don't think I'm the one who can find you.
如果是因为弗雷娅 我可以告诉你...
If this is because Freya, I told you...
你已经说过了
You did.
你说过你对她没感觉
You told me that you don't have feelings for her.
你可以对我撒谎 但你不能对自己撒谎
And you can lie to me if you want, but you should stop lying to yourself.
好运 基利安
Good luck, Killian.
你们还有什么书呢?
Okay, what else have you got?
- 不是吧 - 说来听听
- Come on. - Hit me.
这些你都看完了吗?
You finished those already?
我看书做笔记都非常快的
I am an unbelievably fast note-taker.
这算是我的天赋吧
It's... it's quite a skill.
我不知道我们这儿还有多少关于东区的历史书
I don't know how many more history books on East End that we have.
事实上我在找一些关于...
I'm actually looking for something more about...
神灵 巫术 诅咒 幽灵一类的东西
The occult. Witchcraft, curses, spirits, that kind of thing.
为什么?
Why?
我想你一定已经意识到了
Well, I'm sure you're already aware of this,
这个小镇的神话传说有很长的历史了
but this town has a long history of supernatural legends,
从早期的殖民者到焚烧女巫再到...
from the early settlers to the witch burnings on to...
费尔黑文阿奇博尔德・布朗宁和他的信徒
Archibald Browning and his cult at Fair Haven.
东区一直以东部海岸
You know, East End is also famous for being one
南瓜生长最好的小镇而出名
of the best pumpkin-growing towns on the Eastern Seaboard.
英格丽德写过一篇关于巫术的论文
Uh, Ingrid wrote her dissertation about witchcraft.
有意思 她... 没有跟我提过
Interesting. She didn't... mention it to me.
除非我很讨厌某人 否则我不会跟别人聊
It's not something I usually slip into conversation
这些事情的
unless I want to bore someone.
- 她也会巫术 - 巴布 别说了
- She also does witchcraft. - Barb, stop.
- 不 巴布 接着说 - 我真是太傻了
- No, Barb, continue. - This is stupid.
她让我怀孕了
She got me pregnant.
不 这听起来不太对
Okay. No, that sounds wrong.
我意思是她念了一个怀孕的咒语我才怀孕的
I meant she did a fertility spell for me that made it possible.
那咒语是假的 是我在网上学的
It was a fake spell I got off the Internet
说不定是一个十一岁的孩子写的
probably written by an 11-year-old boy.
跟你怀孕没任何关系
It had nothing to do with you getting pregnant.
根本没有巫术这回事
There's no such thing as witchcraft.
好吧 你跟我肚子里这个
Well, tell that to this thing inside me
每天早上让我呕吐的小家伙说吧
that makes me throw up every morning.
她很搞笑
She's funny.
看起来我们有很多东西可以聊
Sounds like we have a lot more to talk about.
事实上 不行 我现在还有很多工作要做
Uh, actually, no. I got a lot of work to do right now.
我哪儿也不去
Well, I'm not going anywhere.
- 好吧 - 那我们待会儿聊
- Okay. - So, we can talk later.
- 好的 - 好的
- Yes. - All right.
我刚刚看到艾米了 她去哪儿了?
Didn't I just see Amy? Where is she?
她走了 刚跟她分手了
She left. Just broke up with her.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
我想她要的是一段认真的恋爱 而我...
Well, I felt like she was interested in something serious and...
不够认真
I'm not.
你在做什么呀 基利安?
What are you doing, Killian?
- 什么意思? - 我是说 这儿
- What do you mean? - I mean, here.
你的人生 你怎么还能在这儿呢?
With your life. Why are you even still here?
你怎么能在伤害了一个人之后还在这儿呢?
Why be here at all if you're just hurting people?
弗雷娅 我觉得你没有资格批评我
I don't think you're in a position to judge me, Freya.
弗雷娅・波尚在这儿吗?
Is there a Freya Beauchamp here?
是的 在那边
Yeah, just over there.
这是给你的
These are for you.
- 在这儿签字 - 谢谢
- I just need you to sign. - Thanks.
我的天...
Oh, my...
我的天呐 是达什送的
Oh, my God. They're from Dash.
你确定吗? 卡片上又没有名字
You sure about that? No name on the card.
当然是达什送的 还能是谁呢?
Of course they're from Dash. Who else would they be from?
天呐
Oh, my God.
找到了
Got it.
温迪 别着急
Wendy, don't worry.
我有办法了
I have an idea.
温迪...?
Wendy...?
基利安
Killian.
妈妈
Hey, Mom.
- 你可以走了吗? - 可以了 弗雷娅
- Are you ready to go? - Yeah, sure. Freya.
我现在要出去一下 一小时后回来
I'm going out on my break. Be back in an hour.
佩内洛普 很高兴见到你
Penelope, it's so nice to see you.
亲爱的 你还好吗?
Dear, are you all right?
- 你看起来很糟糕 - 什么?
- You look terrible. - What?
- 说真的 你怎么啦? - 你说什么?
- Seriously, what's wrong? - What do you mean?
首先 你一直在... 发抖
Well, for one thing, you keep... swaying.
- 是吗? - 你看上去脸都青了
- Oh, I do? - You look positively green.
跟我来 我带你回家
Come with me. I'm taking you home.
我... 我还没下班呢
Oh, I... My shift isn't over.
跟我走吧
I insist.
我想基利安会替你一会儿的
I'm sure Killian can cover for you.
我们晚点再吃午饭吧
We'll have to take a rain check on our lunch.
好的 当然了 没问题
Yeah, of course. No problem.
但是我还没有下班
But I can't leave work.
你再待下去就要生病了
You can't stay here if you're getting sick.
赶紧走吧 亲爱的
Now come on, dear.
我保证我会好好照顾你的
I promise to take very good care of you.
- 你还好吧? - 是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
我找到一个可能有用的咒语
I found a spell that may work.
需要的东西都有 但是我要... 准备一下
I have what we need but I'll need to... prepare.
如果我们做的对的话也许可以留下这把钥匙
I think we can save the key if we get it right.
我觉得没这个必要
I don't think that'll be necessary.
温迪...
Wendy...
这把钥匙可以解决我们的问题
This key is the answer to our problems.
用它我们就可以回家了
We can use it to go back home.
温迪 停下来
Wendy, stop.
毒液正在控制你
The venom's getting to you.
我们刚刚谈过了 我们不能回去
We just talked about it. We can't go back.
或许现在已经安全了
Maybe it's safe by now.
看着我 那里永远都不会安全的
Look at me. It'll never be safe.
所以我还没用巨蛇
That's why I haven't used the serpent.
也许你错了呢
Maybe you're wrong.
你知道我们不是自愿离开的
You know we didn't leave by choice.
父亲当权的时候把我们放逐到这个世界
Our father banished us to this world when he came into power.
- 但是... - 不!
- But... - No!
他说如果我们回去仙宫 他就会杀了我们
He said if we ever returned to Asgard, he will kill us.
也许他变了呢
But maybe he's changed.
- 他不会变的 - 你不知道
- He hasn't changed. - You don't know that.
我只剩一条命了 乔安娜
I have one life left, Joanna,
我不想浪费在这儿 我想回家
and I don't want to spend it here. I want to go home.
- 你是永生的 你不懂 - 温迪 听我说
- You're immortal. You don't understand. - Wendy, please listen,
你现在要集中精力
I need you to focus.
- 如果我打开入口... - 不!
- If I could just get to the portal... - No!
绝对不能
Absolutely not.
如果打开入口
If that portal opens,
我们不知道另一边会过来什么东西!
we have no idea what may come through from the other side!
那条蛇正在诱惑你达到它的目的
The snake is seducing you to get what it wants.
它的目的就是打开入口
It only wants to open the portal.
那也是我希望的
That's all I want.
我想回家 那儿比这里要好
I miss my home. It was better there.
我也想 温迪 但那已经不是以前的样子了
I miss it, too, Wendy, but it's not the same place anymore.
- 妈咪嘛咪哄! - 不!
- Claude ianuas! - No!
乔安娜...!
Joanna...!
乔安娜!
Joanna!
妈咪嘛咪哄!
Aperite!
你这个贱人
You are such a bitch.
成熟点吧 乔安娜
Grow up, Joanna.
你不能把我永远困在这儿
You can't keep me in here forever.
我会解开咒语的 你知道我一定会的
I will break this spell eventually. You know I will.
这与你无关
This has nothing to do with you.
我是在帮助你
I'm trying to help you.
想帮助我就让我走!
You can help me by letting me go!
我们一定得把这东西从你身上取下来
We have got to get this thing off of you.
你在开玩笑吗?!
Are you kidding me?!
你一点都不关心我
You don't care about me.
你一百多年没有跟我说话
You didn't speak to me for over a hundred years.
你是个冷血的贱人
I guess you're a coldhearted bitch.
去问问弗雷德里克
Just ask Frederick.
对了 你不能 因为你抛弃他了
Oh, that's right. You can't. Because you left him behind.
你抛弃了你唯一的儿子
You abandoned your only son.
- 事情不是那样的 - 不是吗?
- That is not true. - It's not?
你没有抛弃他吗?
You didn't abandon him?
是他不跟我们走 你知道他背叛我了
He refused to come with us. You know that he was turned against me.
你知道吗 对某些人来说...
You know, for somebody...
说起来是养育
supposedly so nurturing,
你所做的就只是毁掉别人
all you seem to do is destroy people.
这就是你不能谈起弗雷德里克的原因
That's why you can't talk about Frederick.
因为你无法改变你对他所做的事
Because you can't deal with what you did to him.
或者你只是... 毫不关心
Or maybe you... just don't care.
你这话太伤人了... 温迪
It broke my heart, Wendy.
我没有一天不后悔把他留在那
There's not a day that goes by that I don't regret leaving him there.
你觉得如果你告诉女孩们
What do you think the girls are gonna say
你撇下了她们的哥哥她们会怎么想?
when I tell them that you left their brother behind?
- 够了 - 那就对了
- Stop it. - Oh, that's right.
其实也没什么关系 不是吗?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
反正她们很快就会死掉
Because they're gonna die soon anyway.
一般都是这个时候 对吧 乔安娜?
It always happens around this time. Right, Joanna?
滴答 滴答
Ticktock. Ticktock.
- 滴答 - 够了
- Ticktock. - That's enough.
我刺激到某人了吗?
Did I strike a nerve?
解开束缚
Liber a vinculis.
我感觉很糟糕 我怎么了?
I feel worse. Wha's wrong with me?
把这个茶喝了 会管用的
Drink this tea. It'll help.
我的胳膊没有知觉了
I can't feel my arms.
嗯 让我帮你吧
Oh, well, let me help.
达什今天给我送花了
Dash sent me flowers today.
太好了 亲爱的
Oh, that's wonderful, dear.
- 那他一定是原谅你了 - 他是我的真爱
- That must mean he forgives you. - He's my soul mate.
他当然是 再喝点
Of course he is. Have some more.
我感觉好困
I just feel so sleepy.
我要躺一会
I'm gonna lay down.
很好 你睡吧
Oh, that's good. You sleep.
酒精稀释...
Vinum attenuat...
...调剂
...Eam.
嗨
Hey.
我很快就走 我保证
I'm leaving soon. I promise.
只是... 这比我旅馆的房间好多了
It's just... it's so much nicer here than my hotel room.
慢慢来 我又发现一本书可能会有用
Take your time. I found one more that might be useful.
太好了
Great.
我没告诉你我的论文
I did not tell you about my dissertation,
你也没告诉我你是一个出版作家
but you didn't tell me you're a published author.
想不到真有图书馆会收藏这本书
I can't believe there's a library that actually stocks this.
它不怎么畅销
It wasn't exactly a bestseller.
是啊 我们有呢 而且我希望你能帮我签名
Well, we have it, and I would like for you to sign it for me.
图书馆不是有规定不能在书上写字吗?
Isn't there some kind of rule about writing in library books?
如果你不说的话 我也不会说出去的
I won't tell, if you don't.
谢谢 那么 这是关于什么的?
Thank you. So, what's it about?
我不想剧透 你还是自己看吧
I don't want to spoil it for you, so you'll just have to read it yourself.
好吧
Deal.
谢谢 英格丽德 谢谢你的帮助
Thank you, Ingrid, for all of your help.
没你的帮忙这需要很久的
This would be taking so much longer without you.
即使对极速读者来说也是吗?
Even for Super Speed Reader Guy?
是的 对他也是一样
Yes, even for him.
那么 你有我的书了
So, you have my book.
我什么时候能看看你的论文?
When do I get to read your dissertation?
不 不可能 我... 我写不完了
Oh, no. That is not happening. I... I never even finished it.
为什么?
Why not?
我... 我觉得对魔法的学术研究太荒谬了
I... I realized that an academic study of witchcraft was kind of ridiculous.
这么说你不相信神喽
Ah, so you don't believe in the supernatural.
不相信
No.
我一直是个科学怀疑论者
Mm-mm. I'm a rational skeptic, all the way.
那样的话 等我完成了
In that case, you probably shouldn't read the book I'm working on.
- 你也不该读我的作品 - 为什么不呢?
- If I ever finish it. - Why not?
我喜欢读科幻小说啊
I like science fiction and fantasy.
- 这不是幻想 - 真的吗?
- It's not fantasy. - Really?
这是关于女巫的 而且...
It is about witches, but...
我相信女巫是存在的
I believe witches are real.
有意思
Funny.
你在哪 温迪?
Where are you, Wendy?
你不能去那个入口
You are not going into that portal.
不!
No!
怎么 你打算杀了我吗? 这是你的计划吗?
So, what, are you gonna kill me? Is that the plan?
有必要的话我会的... 除非你先杀了我
If I have to... Unless you kill me first.
你忘了 我是永生的
You forget, I'm immortal.
我现在知道怎么杀你了
But now I know what'll kill you.
这个东西给了我很多好主意
This is giving me all kinds of good ideas.
那个东西在影响你
That thing's infecting you.
你不能相信它告诉你的
You can't believe what it's telling you.
不 它开阔了我的眼界
No, it's opened my eyes.
现在我知道你是一个恶魔 乔安娜
I now see that you're the evil one, Joanna.
难怪你丈夫离你而去
No wonder your husband left you.
唯一一个你真心爱过的男人
The only man that you ever really truly loved.
你一样毁了他!
And you destroyed him as well!
别把他扯进来 温迪
Leave him out of this, Wendy.
姑娘们也不知道那些 对吧?
The girls don't know about that one, either, do they?
你怎么和她们说她们的父亲的?
What have you told them about their father?
她们有权利知道她们的父亲还活着
Don't they have a right to know that he's alive
并且近在眼前吧?
and so close by?
他很久之前就离开了
He left a long time ago.
他知道我们在哪 他选择了离开
He knows where we are. He chooses to stay away.
我好奇他为什么选择离开
I wonder why he chooses to stay away.
是因为他无法忍受你了吗?
Is it because he can't stand the sight of you?
如果是的话 我可以理解
Because that one, I can understand.
还是他无法原谅你抛下了弗雷德里克
Or is it that he can't forgive you for leaving Frederick behind.
还是因为他无法忍受...
Or is it losing the girls...
不断地不断地失去女儿们
Over and over and over again,
而且因为你的错误她们才被诅咒的?
because it's your fault that they're cursed?
够了!
Stop!
我知道这听起来...
I understand how it sounds...
我过去也是个无神论者...
I used to be a skeptic, too...
但是我看到了证据...
but I've seen evidence...
我见过令人信服的证据...
I've seen convincing evidence...
证据可能是假的
Evidence can be faked.
真的有巫师的 英格丽德
There are real witches, Ingrid,
活在我们中间 很好的隐藏着
living among us, hiding right in plain sight.
我相信他们很久以前从另一个世界来到这里
I believe they came here a very long time ago from a different world.
- 仙宫 - 仙宫? 那是神话里的
- Asgard. - Asgard? This place is a myth.
我认为它是真的
I think it's real,
而且我认为它是和这个镇连着的
and I think it's actually connected to this very town.
所以你觉得有另一个世界
So you believe there's this other world
那里会魔法的人能够来到这里
of magical people who can find their way here.
你用这种语气说出来 的确听起来很疯狂
Well, when you say it in that tone of voice, of course it sounds crazy.
对不起 我只是 只是一时很难相信
I'm sorry, it's just, it's hard to wrap your head around it.
听着 我没有说这个地方一定存在
Look, I'm not saying it's definitely real.
我只是...
I just...
希望它存在
Hope it is.
我父亲整个成年时代都在找这个地方
My father spent his entire adult life looking for it.
- 他也是作家吗? - 不 是个考古学家
- Was he a writer, too? - No. An archaeologist.
他... 专心于证实
He was... obsessed with proving
这个神奇的地方的真实存在
that this mythical world was a real place.
当然 人们都认为他疯了
Of course, people thought he was insane.
而最后果真那样了... 他确实疯了
And eventually it came true... He did lose his mind.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没事 没关系 几年前他去世了
No. It's okay. He died a couple years ago,
但是在他去世之前 他给我看了他的成果
but before he went, he shared his work with me,
恐怖的是 那些都讲得通
and... the scary thing is, it all makes sense.
我必须证明我的父亲没有疯
I have to prove my father wasn't crazy.
我一直研究他的成果
I've been going through his work,
把所有的东西汇总 联系起来
putting together the pieces, connecting the dots,
而后我发现了去仙宫的门
and what I think I've discovered the door to Asgard
就在这里 就在东区
is here, in East End.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Potionem... hanc...
tollam...
妈咪嘛咪哄
viribus...
tuis.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Dona mihi...
...ero.
你真的要惹恼我了 温迪
You're starting to really piss me off, Wendy.
马上结束吧!
This ends right now!
会的... 但不是你希望的那样
Oh, it will... But not the way you hope.
你一直拿着这把钥匙!
You had this key the whole time!
我们没必要困在这 这个困扰我们的地方
We didn't have to be stuck here, where we're persecuted,
这个需要隐藏我们本质的地方
where we have to hide our true nature.
你为什么不想回去?!
Why don't you want to go back?!
因为我们在这比那更安全
Because we're safer here than there.
不会持续太久的
Not for long.
妈咪嘛咪哄!
Axicia volant!
反应很快嘛 亲爱的
Ooh, nice reflexes, babe.
你带那个东西过久 你就不再是你了
You keep that thing on much longer, you'll never be yourself again.
这么久毒素已经深入你的血液了
It's been pumping poison into your veins this whole time.
那你必须毁了它才能从我身上取下来
Then you'll have to destroy it to get it off me,
我知道为了弗雷德里克你不会的
and I know that you can't because of Frederick.
我猜你很为难 对吗?
So I guess you're in a bit of a pickle, aren't you?
- 温迪... 别这样 - 妈咪嘛咪哄!
- Wendy... come on. - Omnia telavolant!
妈咪嘛咪哄
Axicia...
interficiam serpens.
我父亲在秘鲁挖出来的这个
My father found this on a dig in Peru.
他相信这个...
He believed that this...
是去仙宫的地图
was a map to Asgard.
你看 它已经退色了
As you can see, though, it's very faded.
这是个很有意思的符号
That is an interesting symbol.
- 他认为那个是什么意思? - 他不知道
- What did he think that meant? - Uh, he didn't know.
他相信这个和巫术有关
He thought it had something to do with witchcraft,
但是... 他没能破解
but... he couldn't crack it.
我也没弄明白 但是...
I haven't figured it out, either, but...
这不会妨碍我接着尝试
that's not gonna stop me from trying.
嗨? 有人在家吗?
Hello? Anybody home?
妈妈 你在吗?
Mom, are you here?
- 怎么了? - 快点! 拿你的医药箱!
- What's going on? - Hurry! Get your medical bag!
看来为了这本书你的确找了很多材料
Well, it sure seems like you have a lot of material for this book of yours.
我知道
I know.
我也许该继续
I should probably get going.
我还有一本书要看
There's just one more book I need to look at.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Ostende te.
Absconde Te.
- 看到什么有趣的东西了吗? - 没有
- See anything interesting on there? - No.
这个... 你说得对 这个太旧了
It, uh... I think you're right, it's just too worn out.
是啊
Yeah.
她怎么了?
What's wrong with her?
我基本感觉不到心跳
I can barely feel the pulse.
这里到底发生什么事了?
What the hell happened here?
我... 我不知道
I... I don't know.
我们当时在喝茶 她突然就倒了
We were having tea, and she just suddenly collapsed.
- 多久了? - 我不知道
- How long ago? - I don't know,
只是... 你来之前一两分钟
just... one or two minutes before you got here.
我该打911吗?
Should I call 911?
她过敏了 她的血压在降低
She's in anaphylaxis. Her blood pressure's dropping.
她呼吸困难 我都能听到她喉咙闭合的声音
Her breathing's labored. I can practically hear her throat closing up.
你要干什么?
What are you going to do?
她需要一针肾上腺素 马上
She needs a shot of epinephrine, now.
妈咪嘛咪哄! 妈咪嘛咪哄!
Aperio! Aperio!
温迪?
Wendy?
妈咪嘛咪哄!
Aperio!
- 你出不去的 - 等着瞧吧
- You'll never get out. - Watch me.
看 现在你也被困住了
So, now you're trapped, too.
- 放开我 - 让我走 我就放开你
- Let me go. - Let me go, and I will.
不 我不能这么做
No. I can't do that.
好了 你血压正常了 太好了
Well, your blood pressure's normal, so that's good.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你今天吃什么了?
What did you eat today?
我是说 你觉得是什么原因造成的?
I mean, what do you think could've caused this?
我不知道 只是... 感觉好模糊
I don't know. It's just... it's all so foggy.
很高兴你及时出现了
I'm just glad you got here when you did.
是啊 我们还是应该把你送到医院 以防万一
Yeah, we should probably get you to the hospital, though, just to be safe.
不用 不 我没事了 真的
No, no, no, no. I'm okay. Really.
有需要的话尽管告诉我 好吗?
You let me know if you need anything, all right?
你怎么这么快就从伦敦回来了?
So, how did you get back from London so fast?
我没去参加会议
I didn't go to the conference.
我坐飞机到伦敦
I flew to London,
我下了飞机然后...
I got off the plane and...
我真的做不到
I just couldn't do it.
做不到什么?
Couldn't do what?
我做不到没处理好我们之间的事情
I couldn't sit through all those seminars
就坐在那里参加会议
knowing things weren't settled with us.
我做不到... 明知道我们之间还闹着矛盾
I couldn't have this... an ocean between us
却离你这么远
knowing things weren't okay.
所以我转身往回走了
So I turned around and I came right back.
我回来是想告诉你 在你做了这些之后
I came back to tell you that I can't marry you.
我不能再娶你了
Not after what you did.
好吧
Okay.
然后我看见你...
And then I saw you...
快要死了...
About to die...
我意识到我不想生活在一个没有你的世界里
And I realized that I don't want to live in a world where you don't exist.
这种想法让我无法承受
The thought is unbearable.
我也无法承受
It's unbearable to me, too.
我觉得我失去你就像毁了我的一生
I thought I lost you and it was like my life was destroyed.
我再也不会伤害你了 我发誓
I will never hurt you again. I promise.
还是发誓不要再这么吓我了吧
Just promise you'll never scare me like that again either.
我发誓
I promise.
我爱你 弗雷娅
I love you, Freya.
- 永远爱你 - 我也爱你
- Always. - I love you, too.
谢谢你为我开门到这么晚
Thank you for keeping this place open so late for me.
没什么 就看做是我反叛的行为吧
No problem. This is what counts as rebellious for me.
嘿 希望我那一番有关神秘都市
Hey, I hope I didn't freak you out
神秘入口和女巫的事 没有吓坏你
with all that talk of mythical cities, and magical portals and witches.
我发誓我不像起初看上去那么疯狂
I swear I'm not as crazy as I seem at first.
不 我没觉得你疯狂
No, I don't think you're crazy.
我只是觉得我们有不同的爱好
I just think we have different interests.
有关女巫的事我已经放下很长时间了
I left all that witch stuff behind a long time ago,
不知道还能帮你多少
so, I don't know how much more help I can be to you.
好
Okay.
英格丽德 你没生什么气 对吧?
Ingrid, you're not angry about something, are you?
我很抱歉要是说了什么...
'Cause I'm sorry if I said something...
不 没有 我只是有点累了 都这么晚了
No, not at all. I think I'm just tired. Long night.
懂了 我欠你个人情
I get it, and I owe you one.
要是你决定完成你的论文
If you decide to finish your dissertation,
我会很高兴帮助你的
I'd be more than happy to help.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Night.
你知道 只要你打开这扇门
You know, all you have to do is open the door,
所有的一切就都结束了
and this will all be over.
让我走自己的路吧
Just let me go on my way.
你再也不必见到我了
You never have to see me again.
我不会这么做的
I won't do it.
好的 那我就会勒住你
Okay. Then I'll strangle you
直到你昏过去
until you pass out
然后我会带你穿过入口把你作为贡品献出去
and I'll take you through the portal and I'll offer you as a sacrifice.
你会死去 而我会活下来
You'll die, I'll live.
这把钥匙让我如此有力量
Oh, this key is giving me so much more strength.
我好喜欢
I like it.
这应该不需要很久的
This shouldn't take much time.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Ianua.
不要...!
No...!
乔安娜!
Joanna!
妈咪嘛咪哄
Dissolvere.
你没事了
You're okay.
这应该就能止血了
This should stop the bleeding.
我会... 我稍后会帮你疗伤
And I'll... I'll heal you later.
我... 我还要花点时间
I just... I'm just going to take a minute.
你住手吧 我没事的
Will you stop it. I'm fine.
请让我继续我的工作
Let me do my job. Please.
好的
All right.
我想明天带你去医院 做些血液检查
I want to get you to the hospital tomorrow, run some blood tests.
是的 医生
Yes, Doctor.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
我知道
I know.
听着 今晚发生的事很严重
Look, what happened tonight was serious.
你知道 我差点失去你
You know, I almost lost you.
你相信命运吗?
Do you believe in fate?
不怎么信
Not really.
好吧 我信
Well, I do.
我觉得有些事是命中注定的
I believe certain things are written in the stars.
就像我们
Like us.
我们是注定要在一起的
We're meant to be.
我等不及要娶你了
I can't wait to call you my wife.
不过你得休息一下 我去洗个澡
But you need to get some rest. I'm gonna take a shower.
嘿 我来生火 好吗?
Hey, I'm gonna start a fire, okay?
用壁炉旁边的火柴
Use the matches next to the fireplace.
妈咪嘛咪哄!
Luce, igni!
火柴向我走来
Uh... matches come toward me.
妈咪嘛咪哄
eniat ad me arca archa.
这是怎么...?
What is...?
什...?
Wh...?
我为我做的事感到抱歉
I'm so sorry for everything I said.
这不是你的错... 是那条蛇
It wasn't your fault... it was the snake.
对 不过是因为我的原因
Yeah, but because of me,
你毁了能见到儿子的唯一机会
you destroyed your only chance to ever see your son again.
要不然你可能就会永远变成一只怪物
It was either that or let you be a monster forever.
要是你恨我的话我也理解
I understand if you hate me.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
你说得对 我本应该很早以前就毁掉那把钥匙
You were right, I should have destroyed the key a long time ago.
我只是... 我只是还抱有希望
I was just... I was just holding onto the hope
有一天我可能还会见到我儿子
that I might see my son again someday.
不过这不是真的 这...
But it wasn't real. It was...
这只是一个愿望...
It was just a hope and...
我不想承认这个事实...
I mean, I hate to admit it...
...他真的已经走了
...He really is gone.
他已经走了
He's gone.
我不停地想起他 我好想他
I think about him all the time. I miss him so much.
我也是
So do I.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嘿
Hey.
这里到底怎么了?
What the hell happened in here?
- 没什么 - 说来话长
- It's nothing. - Long story.
你呢? 今天过得怎么样?
What about you? How was your day?
很奇怪
Strange.
真的有个叫仙宫的地方吗?
Is there a real place called Asgard?
我要吐了
I'm gonna throw up.
天哪 这是真的
Oh, my God, it's true.
那就是我们的故乡?
And that's where we came from?
- 谁告诉你...? - 你怎么...?
- Who told you...? - How did you...?
图书馆有个男孩 是个作家
This guy at the library, a writer.
他不是我们的同类 不过他试图找到...
He's not one of us, but he's tryin' to find the door...
去仙宫的那扇门 他确定那扇门就在东区
To Asgard. He's convinced it's in East End.
太棒了
Great.
好吧 那扇门被锁住了
Well, that door is locked.
永久地锁住了 再也没有人出入
Forever. No one's going in or out.
总会有一些人试图证明神话是真实存在的
There've always been mortals trying to prove the myths are real.
别理他
Don't even humor him.
如果我是你 我会尽可能的躲着他
I'd just stay away from him as much as possible, if I were you.
好 我会的
Yeah, I will.
- 嘿 - 嘿 亲爱的...
- Hey. - Hey, sweetheart...
- 嘿... - 嘿
- Hey... - Hey.
那... 达什回来了一切都正常了
So... Dash is back and everything seems to be okay.
- 好诶... - 这太棒了!
- Good... - That's great!
我的能量丧失了
My powers are gone.
什么...?
What...?
谢谢你 弗雷娅...
Thank you, Freya...